Evil in ink.
The Tattooist is a horror, thriller film directed by Peter Burger.
American tattoo artist Jake Sawyer wanders the world, exploring
and exploiting ethnic themes in his tattoo designs.
At a tattoo expo in Singapore, he gets his first glimpse at the exotic world of traditional Samoan
tattoo (tatau), and, in a thoughtless act, unwittingly unleashes a powerful angry spirit.
In his devastating journey into Pacific mysticism, Jake must find a way
to save his new love, Sina and recover his own soul.
Jake Sawyer, played by Jason Behr.
Sina, played by Mia Blake.
Mr. Va'a, played by David Fane.
Alipati, played by Robbie Magasiva.
Victoria, played by Caroline Cheong.
Crash, played by Michael Hurst.
The Tattooist is a 2007 New Zealand horror film directed by Peter Burger and starring
Jason Behr, Nathaniel Lees, Michael Hurst and Robbie Magasiva among others.
The film is the first in a series of official
co-productions between New Zealand and Singapore.
The film explores themes of singapore, new zealand, mystic, evil spirit, ghost.
The tone is dark and intense.